#2 "Cinderella Doesn't Smile"
Who was it?
Huh?
Who sent me this letter?
Oh, no! My eyes just met Makabe-kun's!
No way! Mine, too!
Could it be Adagaki Aki?
No... She wouldn't do anything
underhanded like send a letter.
If she were going to expose me,
she'd wait for the perfect moment
when it'd be the most effective.
Moleo
Then who knows about my past?
What? What's up?
Er, um...
Could it actually be him?
What's wrong, Makabe-kun?
You've got a scary look on your face.
O-Oh, it's you, Class Rep.
Isn't that pig's foot unreal?
Are you okay, Makabe-kun?
This guy actually has a
pig's foot in his lunch today.
Like, the whole thing? Why?
My mom put it in. I didn't ask for it.
O-Oh... That's what they're talking about.
I don't ever want to relive that
dark time in my past again.
Hey, Pig's Foot. Oink for me.
Say, "I'm going to take over
my dad's company, oink!"
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Even if these girls are nice
to a hottie like me now...
High School Newspaper
Breaking News
The True Identity of Makabe
Masamune from 2-B!
Huh?
No way! That's what Makabe-kun looked like?
I can't say I appreciate this deception.
Makabe, go buy me a drink.
You're used to that, right?
Of course you'd get found out,
even if you try to cover it up.
You've got some nerve for
a guy on the lowest rung.
I'm so disappointed.
No! Stop!
What's the matter, Makabe? Hurry up
and read from the third paragraph.
I'm sorry. It just made me cry a bit.
You're really that moved
by the The Tale of Heike?
Makabe-kun is so sensitive.
No, I need to find the one...
Unknown X, the one who sent
me the "Pig's Foot" letter...
If Adagaki Aki finds out who I am,
my revenge and everything else is done for.
Even after I got adopted by Grandpa
and changed my last name...
Those nightmarish eight years
drenched in sweat and tears
will all be wasted effort.
Who is Unknown X?
What am I supposed to do?
I'm so stressed out, my tummy hurts...
Wh-What the?!
I want a melon bun and a cheese hot dog!
A BL sandwich and—
So this is the lunchtime school
shop race that I've heard about.
Huh? Could that be...
That's definitely Koiwai Yoshino.
U-Um...
Are you okay?
So Heaven, it turns out,
is just like school.
Er, this isn't Heaven, and you're still alive.
Now that I'm dead, I can
finally speak ill of it.
Fate continues to blow its icy
cold breath at me without end.
Period.
What the hell is going on here?
Hey... Koiwai-san?
But... I can't buy them now.
I can't go back.
Explosive Croquette Buns x5
Cutlet Sandwiches x4
Huh? You want me to go buy them?
Yeah...
Why me?!
Tanisaki Bread
Thanks.
All right, next.
F-Five explosive croquette buns
and four cutlet sandwiches.
Sure thing. Thanks.
Holy crap, they're so heavy!
Croquette
Explosive
This must be a dream.
Like the final illusion that
the Little Match Girl saw...
I bought the damn things for you!
One... two... three...
four... five.
You were an umbrella-hat priest statue?
Wha...
Those buns... The one who wants
them is Adagaki-san, not you, right?
Do you mind if I come with you?
I might be able to find out
whether she's Unknown X or not.
Sneak, sneak, sneak...
Hold on a sec.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
After you had that much fun,
it's only natural that you
pay me back with your body.
I'm sowwy...
Sorry, I was just kidding.
I won't do anything that'll get you in trouble.
Really, I promise.
I'll properly explain everything
to her. Don't worry.
Really?
You're just like
Cinderella getting bullied
by her wicked stepmother.
I can totally relate, being a
former "Pig's Foot" myself.
You're late!
Evil Stepmother
The Top Princess
of the School
Do you want me to pass out from hunger?
I'm sorry.
A preschooler on their first shopping
run would be faster than you.
I'm sorry.
Yoshino, you idiot.
And how is she a princess?
Well, this isn't something a hater
like me wants to really see, either.
You okay?
Wh-What are you doing here?
Yoshino?
She ran away, didn't she?
She went to buy some tea
for you.
What are you doing here?
Just dropping by to say hi
and see how you're doing.
She ate all that even before
the bread? Unbelievable.
A-And how are you doing? You know...
Oh, my cut hand?
Well, it just stings when I take a bath,
and it's a bit hard to get dressed.
Actually, it still hurts like hell.
I had no intention of getting you involved.
That's right. Let it hurt
your pride even more.
It's all part of my plan to gain
a mental advantage over you.
Hmph.
Given that things are going
as I'd planned so far,
the "Unknown X" who sent
me the Pig's Foot letter
isn't Adagaki Aki.
Pig's Foot
Then who...
So infuriating.
W-Well, excuse me! Sorry!
Oh, no, no! I wasn't—
I'm back!
You idiot! Don't look!
Close your eyes!
My eyes! My eyes!
Strawberry
Milk
Huh, what? For me, too?
Th-Thank you, Cinderella.
Yoshino is very humble toward everyone.
She's always bowing her head and
fidgeting. It's a horrible habit.
You should stop being so nice to everyone.
What's with that look?
Nothing.
It's fine when she's nice to me.
It's expected for Yoshino to work for me.
No, it's just that you have
cutlet sauce on your nose.
And I can't be nice to everyone, either.
What's that supposed to mean?
Indeed, what could it possibly mean?
Maybe I want you to rely on me
more than you rely on Koiwai-san.
Wh-What's his deal?!
All right! I nailed it!
Aki-sama's probably bright red right now!
Of course she'd develop feelings for a guy
who saved her and even shed blood for her
if he said something like that.
You idiot. I told you I'd be there for you.
I didn't think you'd actually
come to save me.
Don't ever doubt me again.
Onii-chan's reading "Barasute"! Gross!
Bara no Hitomi no Steroid
I'm glad I read Chinatsu's shojo manga!
I can do this!
Now if she falls for me even more...
The "Dead or Love" Plan will
move another step forward!
Idiot.
Next, I need to get her email address.
I've never asked a girl
for her email address,
but at this rate, it won't be a problem!
Pig's Foot.
Are you trying to get back
at Aki-sama, Pig's Foot?
Why do you know my old nickname?!
A little girl like her wasn't among
the kids that bullied me in the past.
Even around Aki...
Huh?
Wait a sec.
She's there!
You used to be at Adagaki's mansion!
Ow...
My family has served the Adagakis
for generations.
We've been nothing but
attendants for 300 years.
She's totally one of
Adagaki Aki's lackeys!
To Cinderella, Aki wasn't
an evil stepmother,
but a master to serve!
It's all over.
I was completely fooled by her
Cinderella-like nature.
My revenge comes to an end here...
If you want to laugh, go ahead and laugh.
I still have no regrets about
trying to give that woman
a taste of her own medicine.
That's fine. Why don't you do it?
I'll even help you out.
What do you think about having a
tea party after school, Aki-sama?
My father bought some macarons from Paris.
Sadly, I have school beautification
committee duties today.
You're amazing, Aki-sama. You're so
passionate about your committee duties.
Too amazing!
What's that Koiwai Yoshino up to?
There's no way I can trust her.
This might be another trap.
I have to do this on my own!
Yeah!
This revenge plan is for me!
I won't change anything!
I need to become email buddies
with her first, as planned.
Masamune-kun!
You can't get back to class that way.
Futaba-san.
Are you still not used to this school?
Want me to make you a map?
Nah, I'd feel bad.
Thanks!
And checking up on transfer students
is part of the class rep's job.
I'll work extra hard for you, Masamune-kun.
Now, come on. This way.
So we've been talking about
having a barbecue as a class.
It'll be a lot of fun.
I'll try it out here first.
So, Futaba-san...
Why don't we exchange email—
Edit
Friends
Add
Profiles
Makabe Masamune
Email... email...
0 Contacts
Huh? Huh?
Asking a girl for her email
address is super hard!
What's the matter, Masamune-kun?
Sorry! I have to get back to class!
What? Let's go together!
H-Hey, Kojuurou! This is
a common sense quiz!
When you exchange email addresses,
the number of contacts you have
will be shared, as well.
True or false?
I think it's false.
Really? You're certain, right?
Lying is the first step to becoming a thief!
Why are you so worried about that?
Because I've never done it, duh!
Don't make me say it! It's embarrassing!
Well, that's good, though.
Exchanging email addresses doesn't
mean she'll find out I'm all alone.
Isn't there some kind of situation
where it wouldn't be awkward
for me to ask for her email address?
Huh? Hold on a sec. That's rather sudden.
Well, you're the class rep, right?
We can't just give class B special treatment.
I'd do it if I didn't have committee and club work.
What's wrong, Futaba-san?
The school beautification
committee lost a member,
so they're looking for someone
to fill in until summer.
Want me to do it?
I haven't joined any committees yet.
Really? Are you sure?
Yeah, if it's for you.
This is my chance!
Makabe-kun, you really came!
I'm so happy! Thank goodness
I'm in this committee!
Oh, please...
Oh, come on! Don't ignore me!
Please begin working.
What am I doing?
"Oh, what a coincidence!
Is this the red string of fate?"
That didn't have to happen,
but you could have reacted
at least a little bit!
I freak out over exchanging email addresses,
I'm a former Pig's Foot, and I'm
deathly scared of spiders.
If people could see into me,
they'd see how worthless I am.
No one would want to go out with me.
Thinking I could make that woman
fall for me like this was crazy.
Sorry, Masamune-kun.
I pushed something really
troublesome onto you.
No...
No, no!
You don't need to feel
responsible for this at all.
It's okay. I know it myself.
I'm always meddling.
I'm nothing like you, someone who
helps without saying a word.
Wait... Wait, wait!
Am I actually in that golden situation
where I'm all alone with a girl?
And she went out of her way to find me?
Class Rep...
Say...
The barbecue should be a lot of fun, too,
but would you like to
go to a movie sometime?
Like, just the two of us?
Movie? By movie, do you mean...
Sitting next to each other, with our
hands touching on the arm rest...
Watching a gory movie, with her
screaming and grabbing on to me...
Going out for drinks later
and talking about the movie,
leading to talking about a relationship?
Basically, what you call a d-d-d-date?
No! I almost forgot my main objective!
U-Um... Right now, I'm...
R-Right. Of course you're busy.
Sorry to ask you out of the blue like that!
No, not at all....
Do your best, Masamune-kun.
Wait... Does this mean I'm popular?
This means I'm popular, right? I'm popular!
Thank you, Futaba-san!
You just gave me an insane
amount of confidence!
What?!
I came to get a new bucket.
Th-Thanks, Adagaki-san.
My expressions... I still can't
control my expressions!
That girl isn't on the school
beautification committee, is she?
That's right. I guess she wanted to talk to me.
Huh? Did you hear us, by chance?
It must be nice, being so popular.
Oh, my. What's this?
Did I just hear a bit of
prickliness in your voice?
Was that jealousy? Well, isn't that cute?
It doesn't matter if some girl I
have no feelings for asks me out.
Really? Then who would
you like to ask you out?
Adagaki-san.
All right, what's it going to be?
The one and only hottie Makabe Masamune-kun
basically just asked you out.
Well? I wouldn't mind going
with you, Adagaki-san.
Thanks.
"Thanks"? "Thanks"?!
W-Well done, Masamune!
You did good. This is what's
supposed to happen.
I-I see... That's good.
Then, um, will you tell
me your email address?
I'll contact you.
Sure.
Huh?
Huh?! Did I just achieve
my goal that easily?!
I'm friggin' awesome! I'm so hot!
Oh, but I'm sorry.
My phone is being repaired right now.
Can I tell you the next
time we're on duty?
Huh? Repairs?
I'm going to lose my rhythm now?
But I guess it can't be helped.
All right. Here, then,
at this time next week.
I've been here forever and
she still hasn't shown up!
Weird...
Look inside the drawer of the teacher's desk
Inside the broom closet?
The desk in the very back?
The animal pen
The animal pen?
It must be that.
Look outside the window
from where you started
from where you started.
How charming can you be, Adagaki Aki?
Here we go!
Exchanging email addresses!
I Decline
Who the hell do you think you are?!
That was rather unfortunate.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to clean in Aki-sama's place.
If you came here to laugh at me, leave.
You're too naïve.
If you leave things to me,
you could exchange email addresses
and go on dates all you want.
D-Dates?
Contacts
Add
Koiwai Yoshino
Cell
See?